Guys, it's been over an hour!
伙计们  已经一个多小时了
I'm worried about your bodies!
我担心你们的身体
Gene, I'm sorry. I-I...
吉恩  我很抱歉  我  我...
Oh, I can't get my legs off this thing.
我没法把腿从这玩意儿上放下来
Do-do you just want me to drop you?
你想让我松开你吗
No! We do this together or we don't do it at all!
不  要么一起  要么不做
Okay. Just... just going to go against all my instincts and plummet to the ground while holding my child
好吧  只要...只要抵抗我所有的本能抱着我的孩子一头栽在地上
Bob, I'm gonna count to three,and if you don't release your legs,
鲍勃  我数到三如果你再不松开腿
I'm gonna charge you for a second trapeze experience. The full price.
我就要再收你一次空中飞人体验费
We'll pay double!
我们付双倍
- Gene, no! - One, two...
-吉恩  不行  -一  二...
- Full price, Bob! - No, no, no!
-全价  鲍勃  -不  不  不
No, I'm...Okay,
不  我正在...
I'm doing it! I'm doing it!
好吧  我在努力  我在努力
Why am I doing it this way?
为什么我要这样
it hurts so much!
太疼了
Dad, release your Krakens!
爸爸  放开你纠缠的大腿
I'm trying, Gene!
我在努力  吉恩